# JOHN MAZZUCCO

johnmazzucco.codes john.mazzucco@gmail.com Mississauga, ON

### **About Me**

I attended Seneca College and graduated with a Computer Networking and Technical Support Diploma. Shortly after, I joined Stewart Title Guaranty Company as an IT Helpdesk Technician. I then made the decision to pursue a career in Web Development and transitioned to a Business and Quality Assurance Analyst role in the Product Development team. There, I worked alongside developers and gained valuable experience, developing strong skills and capabilities. After 5 years with Stewart, I made the decision to focus on my education full-time and enrolled in Bitmaker Labs' Full Stack Web Development course. This was a challenging and intensive program where I learned key foundational skills and current trends in the Web Development space. I am currently seeking an exciting opportunity in the Toronto area as a Junior Web Developer while volunteering as a Web Developer for NeuroTechX, a non-profit organization.

# **Projects**

### **AMAZON AFFILIATES**

A Chrome extension that stores <u>Amazon Affiliate</u> IDs and automatically adds a selected ID to the URL when visiting amazon.com.

#### **SEATYOURSELF**

A clone of <u>OpenTable</u> built with Rails that allows users to find nearby restaurants via Google Geolocation and book fictitious reservations.

#### **CROWDREVIEW**

A Rails app that allows users to search for scientific journal articles using the <u>PLoS</u> API. To improve the performance of the search function, articles are saved to a local database once they are retrieved from the PLoS database. Each article has a comments section and can be added to a "favourites" list by a User.

# Experience

### WEB DEVELOPER, NEUROTECHX; REMOTE - 2016-PRESENT

I am volunteering with a small group of other neurotechnology enthusiasts to create a new website for the <u>NeuroTechX</u> non-profit organization. During this opportunity, I gained experience using the Facebook, Twitter, Meetup and Slack APIs, furthered my understanding of AJAX requests, and learned to code in PHP.

### JR BUSINESS AND QUALITY ASSURANCE ANALYST, STEWART TITLE; TORONTO, ON - 2014-2015

I was a part of a team of 15 analysts and developers that deployed and maintained a web application which was the company's primary channel of sales. My main responsibilities included gathering business requirements, creating user stories, mockups, and thoroughly testing the application with verification and regression testing methods.

### IT HELP DESK TECHNICIAN, STEWART TITLE; TORONTO, ON - 2010-2014

I was on a team of 4 that supported over 200 local and 50 international employees. We responded to user requests and issues regarding computer hardware, software, accounts, permissions, printers, VoIP phones, and smartphones. Some key projects we were responsible for were include upgrading a Nortel phone system to VoIP and rolling out virtual machines to all users.

## Education

Bitmaker Labs, Toronto, ON – Immersive Full Stack Web Development Course, 2015 Seneca College, North York, ON – Computer Networking and Technical Support Diploma, 2009

### **Proficiencies**

HTML5 · CSS3 · Sass · Ruby on Rails · JavaScript · ES6 · ¡Query · AJAX · Node · PHP · REST · TDD